[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 0, "question": "Tonight, is Kim Jong-Il's son just as dangerous as his father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1, "answer": "His dad couldn't be trusted.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim Jong-Il"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "How many times have you been properly loved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "This is PIERS MORGAN TONIGHT.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "If you were President Obama would you be picking the phone up now to the Chinese to make sure there is nothing untoward that now happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, we have a shared interest in the outcome.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "I mean this is just a stunt, isn't it, for western media eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I think that we all think -- are very cynical about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea", "Seoul", "South Korea"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "How dangerous is North Korea right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "North Korea as a state has a considerable blackmailing capability because they have a large concentration of artillery aimed at the city of Seoul, which is the capital of South Korea, and has a very large population.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "When you look at all the candidates for the Republican race to be president, which one of them from their foreign policy statements is the one that you think is most suited to be president of the United States?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I have tried to stay out of the debate but in the Republican Party.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Would you find him sexy through his voice, his brain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Well, the voice alone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Amazing voice, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I mean my pants fell of during the commercial break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "You mean like the old Moviefone guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Moviefone"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "-NONE-", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Who is in charge here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, first of all, my Twitter is called @kathygriffin, and if you want to send them to a real star, send them to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Are you looking forward to humiliating Anderson on New Year's Eve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I really live for that night.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wolf Blitzer"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "I'm going to drunk dial Wolf Blitzer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What is a roofie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Are there cards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I just haven't heard it called a roofie before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you fancy him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I do fancy him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "``", "JJ", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Can you save this shameless plug until later?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Well, the name of the special is funny, \"Tired Hooker.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "You're not going to go back to Dr. Kissinger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I get what I want --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Kissinger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "You must be sad that Herman Cain is not in the race any more, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "RBR", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I'm living.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Who's the biggest nut bag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, it changes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Let me ask you, though, about him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Why wouldn't I be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What's more embarrassing than this moment for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Was that an old time --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "But that is utterly embarrassing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Yes, I know, it was great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "How did you feel when you woke up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Because unlike you, I'm among the people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "And you lost complete control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "May I call you Piersy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "You may call me whatever you like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "What have you still got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "RIFFIN: I've still got a banging bikini bod which is really -- it's a burden at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Are you dating a younger man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "How much younger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Youngerish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Like how many years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "A few.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "More than four years younger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Is he more than 10?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "More than 20 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "So 15 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "You SOB.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Are you and this man on the picture right now having sex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "No, but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Fifteen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I'm excited you think he's legal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you recommend toy boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, I think that there is -- I think I have a better chance of being asked out by a younger guy than a guy my age, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "How old are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I'm 46 but I look younger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "My fourth Grammy nomination in a row.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "You ever won?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you mind just never winning or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "No, I'm bitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Why else would you be there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "No, you're there to win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Unlike you who spent your life on the D-list, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "RIFFIN: No, it's A.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Madonna"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I like how you're basically making me the new Madonna.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Somebody here said, would you date Kim Jong-un, the new leader of North Korea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "He's a little old for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "How much of Kathy Griffin is fake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Do they mean my physical body or my personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy Griffin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Do you know you're on television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How much have you spent looking this young?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, the body part is all real, although I did have lypo one time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "-- thing you spent money on body-wise that you're most proud of?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "None of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Do you know her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "You said if Ryan gets \"The Today Show, you will never be watching it because you hate him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Did you go to Kendall's Super Sweet 16?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kendall"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Don't you admire their work ethic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I don't think I heard you correctly, because I think you said work ethic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "What did you make of the extensive 72-day marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "That's heaven for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Was it a scam or do you think true love just hit a rocky path?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I love that you think they started with true love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "A certain age?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "-- dating a much younger guy and then marrying him -- I mean, do you worry about your position?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I love that you think I have a position.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 619, "question": "I assume we were talking about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Why don't we talk about --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "You must miss it, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Yes, that was so much fun to do that show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "What is the secret to getting away with looking hot in your 60s, 70s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Look, I'm not in the class with those women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Who do you most admire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I admire those chicks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "And you know, Gloria Steinem gave me this great hilarious lecture about how -- can you say vagina on CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "You just did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria Steinem"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Glo Vanderbilt"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "Where are you going with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "This goes -- then I go to Glo Vanderbilt's house, who says no, no, no, don't worry; your vagina is fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What do you got, Piersy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "Probably --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "PRP$", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Are you going to tear me up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "What we call in Britain my P-45.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Who would care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Everyone wants --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Who cares?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "That's a spin-off of \"Little People, Big World.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "What's with my neck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "No idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "Can I be honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "I haven't gotten you fired.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 780, "question": "What is your address, real quick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "You know what you've done --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "What's your phone number?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "You've shown that you can do live TV with the best of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "Did I get bleeped there or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "You're always getting bleeped.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "OK, what's your question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Nothing really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "She's driving up or what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "There we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "What do you think of Lindsay Lohan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "I love her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lindsay Lohan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "I don't know -- how can I help you get off the desk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "Because the only possibly useful thing about you is you are well connected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 848, "question": "Can you get me Cher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 849, "answer": "I'm sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 853, "question": "Did you come out during the commercial break?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 854, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Are you an openly gay man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "Who turned out to be surprisingly interesting in the chair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "Surprisingly interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "Now that you mention it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "You wanted Kissinger for the hour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kissinger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 929, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 930, "answer": "We couldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 933, "question": "Could be better than you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 934, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 938, "question": "But why on Earth would he ever sit down with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 939, "answer": "Because he has given no television interview in 40 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 942, "question": "What do you bring to the table, Morgan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 943, "answer": "I'm a huge fan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morgan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 964, "question": "Why should anybody watch it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 965, "answer": "It's very funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 971, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 972, "answer": "You are insane.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 976, "question": "How many times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 977, "answer": "Have I properly been in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 993, "question": "If I could give you five minutes to live, and you could relive any moment of your life, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 994, "answer": "It would -- I would relive the first five minutes of this show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1018, "question": "Why are you never serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1019, "answer": "No, I'm just not serious with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1020, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1021, "answer": "I have trust issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]